<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cockatrice_carddatabase version="4">
  <cards>

    <card>
      <name>SWTG 3+Color Archetypes</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors></colors>
        <type></type>
        <maintype></maintype>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>1</tablerow>
      <text>GWU JEDI ORDER Jedi have abilities that trigger when they enter or leave the battlefield. They recur these with the Meditate mechanic returning them to your hand.
WUB SEPARATISTS The Separatist Droid army uses the Repair mechanic to allow you to eventually recast your Droids from the graveyard.
UBR SITH EMPIRE Sith get stronger with the Hate mechanic, granting stronger effects or new abilities if an opponent has lost life from anything but combat damage.
BRG BOUNTY HUNTERS Criminals and bounty hunters place bounty counters on opposing creatures and reward you when those creatures die.
RGW THE WILDS Wookiees, Ewoks, and large beasts use the Monstrosity mechanic to get larger and have abilities that care about being monstrous.
WUBRG TROOPER LEGION Every trooper has an ability that strengthens all your troopers.</text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Tusken Raider</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>W</colors>
        <type>Token Creature - Tusken </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt></pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text></text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>TIE Fighter</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>B</colors>
        <type>Token Artifact - Vehicle </type>
        <maintype>Artifact</maintype>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>1</tablerow>
      <text>Spaceflight (This creature can only block or be blocked by creatures with spaceflight.)
Crew 1 (Tap any number of creatures you control with total power 1 or greater: This Vehicle becomes an artifact creature until end of turn.)</text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Droid</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors></colors>
        <type>Token Artifact Creature - Droid </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>1/1</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text></text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Trooper</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>W</colors>
        <type>Token Creature - Trooper </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>1/1</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text></text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Royal Guard</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>R</colors>
        <type>Token Creature - Trooper </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>2/2</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text>First strike</text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Rebel</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>W</colors>
        <type>Token Creature - Rebel </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>1/1</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text></text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>B-Wing</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>U</colors>
        <type>Token Kindred Artifact - Rebel Vehicle </type>
        <maintype>Artifact</maintype>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>1</tablerow>
      <text>Spaceflight (This creature can only block or be blocked by creatures with spaceflight.)
Crew 1 (Tap any number of creatures you control with total power 1 or greater: This Rebel Vehicle becomes an artifact creature until end of turn.)</text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Ewok Rebel</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>G</colors>
        <type>Token Creature - Ewok Rebel </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>1/1</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text></text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Bounty Hunter</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>R</colors>
        <type>Token Creature - Mercenary </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>4/4</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text></text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>SWTG 2-Color Archetypes</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors></colors>
        <type></type>
        <maintype></maintype>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>1</tablerow>
      <text>GW REBEL ALLIANCE Play Rebels and their Ewok allies from the original trilogy.
WU JEDI AND DROID ENTERS Play creatures with abilities that trigger when they enter. Use meditate and repair to do it again.
UB DARK SIDE Dark side themed instant and sorcery cards power this control archetype.
BR HATEFUL BOUNTY Complete bounties that deal damage to use your hatred and punish all who stand in your way.
RG MONSTERS AND HUNTERS Use counters to amp up your threats and put bounties on your opponents threats,
GU JEDI ORDER Jedi have abilities that trigger when they enter or leave the battlefield. They recur these with the Meditate mechanic returning them to your hand.
WB SEPARATISTS The Separatist Droid army uses the Repair mechanic to allow you to eventually recast your Droids from the graveyard.
UR SITH EMPIRE Sith get stronger with the Hate mechanic, granting stronger effects or new abilities if an opponent has lost life from anything but combat damage.
BG BOUNTY HUNTERS Criminals and bounty hunters place bounty counters on opposing creatures and reward you when those creatures die.
RW THE WILDS Wookiees, Ewoks, and large beasts use the Monstrosity mechanic to get larger and have abilities that care about being monstrous.</text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Trooper1</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors>W</colors>
        <type>Token Creature - Trooper </type>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <pt>1/1</pt>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
      <text></text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Obi-Wan Kenobi Emblem</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors></colors>
        <type>Emblem</type>
        <maintype>Emblem</maintype>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>1</tablerow>
      <text>Creatures you control get +1/+1 and have vigilance, first strike, and lifelink.</text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Yoda, Jedi Master Emblem</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors></colors>
        <type>Emblem</type>
        <maintype>Emblem</maintype>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>1</tablerow>
      <text>Hexproof, you and your creatures have.</text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Aurra Sing, Bane of Jedi Emblem</name>
      <set>SWTG</set>
      <prop>
        <colors></colors>
        <type>Emblem</type>
        <maintype>Emblem</maintype>
      </prop>
      <tablerow>1</tablerow>
      <text>Whenever a nontoken creature you control leaves the battlefield, discard a card.</text>
      <token>1</token>
    </card>

  </cards>
</cockatrice_carddatabase>